<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title><![CDATA[Meanwhile]]></title>
  <subtitle><![CDATA[Journal • Thoughts • Favourites]]></subtitle>
  <link href="/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://widatama.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-07-05T08:55:42.521Z</updated>
  <id>http://widatama.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Danu Widatama]]></name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://zespia.tw/hexo/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Emi Meyer and The Shanghai Restoration Project]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/emi-meyer/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/emi-meyer/</id>
    <published>2014-07-05T08:37:40.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-05T08:40:46.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Good music and exquisite voice. Perfect summer song.</p>
<iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/2as7ldIdWFs" width="864" height="468" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Music" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Music/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[On The Price of Success]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-the-price-of-success/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-the-price-of-success/</id>
    <published>2014-06-19T02:42:39.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-05T08:35:26.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>When you have nothing, you don&#39;t fear being torn to shreds by the mob. You stand up and you call bullshit when you see it. But then when you start to do well… when you start to make a name for yourself… when you start to make money or have a certain number of Twitter followers, the spotlight turns to you.</p>
<p>You start to be more diplomatic and politically correct. You start to mould yourself into the shape of what everyone else expects you to be, because if you aren‘t that, then the mob is waiting like it’s Lord of The fucking Flies.</p>
<p>Electric fences start to pop up all around you. Issues which you don‘t even go near because touching them, in any way, is fatal. You can’t talk about sexism any more, because one wrong move there is career-ending. You don‘t call out the bullshit industry awards, because you’re nominated to win some of them. You fail to draw attention to the morally bankrupt venture capitalists and journalists, because then they might not write about you or give you money any more.</p>
<p>So you mellow. And slowly but surely you turn into the very thing that you once rebelled against so strongly in your first album. When you had a voice. When you actually fucking stood for something.</p>
<p>And then you can&#39;t talk about anything any more. The fear has taken over. All hope of the change that you once so strongly believed in has now been lost.</p>
<p><strong>The price of success is censorship. We bring it on ourselves, <br/> and we enforce it on others with this giant pyramid scheme <br/> which we call “life”.</strong></p>
<p>…</p>
<p><strong>The price of success is this: You have two choices. Join the bullshit facade and plod along as another sheep in the capitalist machine, doing whatever it takes to maintain your position — or stand up for something you believe in, and accept every kick, punch and vicious attack on who you are.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<div class="source"><a href="http://john.onolan.org/the-price-of-success/" target="_blank">The Price of Success</a> <em>by</em> John O&#39;Nolan</div>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Tribute to Vignelli]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/tribute-to-vignelli/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/tribute-to-vignelli/</id>
    <published>2014-05-28T00:59:51.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-30T04:28:21.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p><span class="scream">In a world where everybody screams</span>, <span class="silence">silence</span> <span class="scream">is noticeable.</span></p>
</blockquote>
<div class="source"><a href="http://observatory.designobserver.com/feature/massimo-vignelli-1931-2014/38336/" target="_blank">Massimo Vignelli, 1931&ndash;2014</a></div>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[On The Caring Ones]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-the-caring-ones/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-the-caring-ones/</id>
    <published>2014-05-09T02:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-17T03:31:24.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>Realize that nobody cares, and if they do, you shouldn‘t care that they care. Got a new car? Nobody cares. You’ll get some gawkers for a couple of weeks—they don‘t care. They’re curious. Three weeks in it‘ll be just another shiny blob among all the thousands of others crawling down the freeway and sitting in garages and driveways up and down your street. People will care about your car just as much as you care about all of those. Got a new gewgaw? New wardrobe? Went to a swanky restaurant? Exotic vacation? Nobody cares. Don’t base your happiness on people caring, because they won&#39;t. And if they do, they either want your stuff or hate you for it.</p>
<p>Occasionally, people in your life will defy the odds and actually care about you. Still not your stuff, sorry. But if they value you, they‘ll value that you value it, and they’ll listen. When you talk about all of those things that nobody else cares about, they will look into your eyes and consume your words, and in that moment you will know that every part of them is there with you.</p>
<p>Marry them. Befriend them. Work with them. <br/> Spend weekends with them. No matter how much power you become possessed of, you&#39;ll never be able to make someone care—so gather close the caring.</p>
</blockquote>
<div class="source"><a href="https://www.quora.com/Justin-Freeman" target="_blank">Justin Freeman</a> <em>on</em> <a href="https://www.quora.com/Life/What-are-the-top-10-things-that-we-should-be-informed-about-in-life" target="_blank">Quora</a></div>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Stop Your Crying]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/stop-your-crying/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/stop-your-crying/</id>
    <published>2014-04-17T01:43:03.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-30T13:04:53.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These guys never fail to amaze me&hellip;</p>
<iframe width="864" height="468" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/UcVbkiVZg7U" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Music" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Music/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[The Luckiest]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/the-luckiest/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/the-luckiest/</id>
    <published>2014-02-11T14:30:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-11T14:08:23.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I was watching <a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt2194499" target="_blank">About Time</a> a couple of days ago and this song came out. Ben Folds makes some really good music, this one is certainly a favourite.</p>
<iframe width="864" height="468" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/S1qL2ynRpXU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Music" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Music/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[On Our Attention to Life]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-our-attention-to-life/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-our-attention-to-life/</id>
    <published>2014-02-01T23:22:56.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-03T13:51:51.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>We have these brief lives, and our only real choice is how we will fill them. Your attention is precious. Don’t squander it. Don’t throw it away. Don’t let companies and products steal it from you. Don’t let advertisers trick you into lusting after things you don’t need. Don’t let the media convince you to covet the lives of celebrities. Own your attention &mdash; it’s all you really have.</p>
</blockquote>
<div class="source"><a href="http://transom.org/?p=41667" target="_blank">Navigating Stuckness</a> <em>by</em> Jonathan Harris</div>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[The Static Temptation]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/the-static-temptation/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/the-static-temptation/</id>
    <published>2014-01-19T00:59:18.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-19T02:38:02.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I have been exploring the options for making this whole site content static. The initial set up is quite a hassle but afterwards there are less things to take care of and less to worry about.</p>
<p>So here it is, static contents made with <a href="http://zespia.tw/hexo" target="_blank">Hexo</a> and hosted on <a href="http://pages.github.com/" target="_blank">Github Pages</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Writing" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Writing/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[On Making Sense of Things]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-making-sense-of-things/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-making-sense-of-things/</id>
    <published>2013-09-13T18:09:41.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-12T14:08:21.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>People don&#8217;t want things to make sense, although they always say they do. Know why? Because if things made sense we&#8217;d all be in trouble. You drive too fast down the street because it feels good or because you&#8217;re in a hurry. Now if things made sense, a cop would stop you every single time and give you a ticket. Now what happens if a cop &#8216;does&#8217; stop you? You get angry and say that&#8217;s not fair! Of course it&#8217;s fair. It also makes sense. But if life made sense we&#8217;d either behave ourselves a hell of a lot better or we&#8217;d be walking around scared, waiting to be punished for all the bad things we do every day. We want life to make sense only when it&#8217;s to our &#8216;advantage.&#8217; Otherwise, it&#8217;s interesting not knowing what&#8217;s coming next. Maybe you&#8217;ll get heads, maybe tails. People do wrong things all the time and get away with them. Good people get their necks broken. Would you prefer it if only the good people got rewarded? How often are you good? How often do you deserve the good <em>you</em> get? Wouldn&#8217;t you rather have an interesting life than a fair one?</p>
</blockquote>
<div class="source"><a href="http://www.jonathancarroll.com/index.php" target="_blank">Jonathan Carroll</a>, author</div>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Lake Street Dive]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/lake-street-dive/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/lake-street-dive/</id>
    <published>2013-07-28T09:30:03.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-18T23:30:44.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What an amazing band. Great, solid music through and through.</p>
<iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/0LhsE-uqqE0" width="864" height="468" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Music" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Music/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[On Small Gestures]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-small-gestures/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-small-gestures/</id>
    <published>2013-05-22T06:59:20.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-07T16:36:19.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>I firmly believe in small gestures: pay for their coffee, hold the door for strangers, over tip, smile or try to be kind even when you don&#8217;t feel like it, pay compliments, chase the kid&#8217;s runaway ball down the sidewalk and throw it back to him, try to be larger than you are particularly when it&#8217;s difficult. People do notice, people appreciate. I appreciate it when it&#8217;s done to (for) me. Small gestures can be an effort, or actually go against our grain (&#8220;I&#8217;m not a big one for paying compliments&hellip;&#8221;), but the irony is that almost every time you make them, you feel better about yourself. For a moment life suddenly feels lighter, a bit more Gene Kelly dancing in the rain.</p>
</blockquote>
<div class="source"><a href="http://www.jonathancarroll.com/index.php" target="_blank">Jonathan Carroll</a>, author</div>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Mr. Sonjaya]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/mr-sonjaya/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/mr-sonjaya/</id>
    <published>2013-05-12T09:30:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-23T15:35:12.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Definitely a gem.</p>
<iframe width="864" height="468" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/j8A2QCJuFH4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

<p>Find more of them <a href="https://soundcloud.com/mrsonjaya" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Music" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Music/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Minimalism]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/minimalism/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/minimalism/</id>
    <published>2013-03-03T02:56:47.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-25T15:54:01.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I have been frequenting <a href="http:://www.reddit.com/r/minimalism">this subreddit</a> lately and I found it really fascinating. I did not know why but this idea of minimalism just felt profound. There was a certain sense of tranquility that I get by seeing all those posts (yes, those pictures of clean desks included).</p>
<p>What I am really interested though is applying minimalism to our life. The idea is simply brilliant. Reduce everything to only what is necessary. This way, we can focus on the most important things and hence get the most out of our life.</p>
]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Writing" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Writing/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Calvin and Hobbes]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/calvin-and-hobbes/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/calvin-and-hobbes/</id>
    <published>2013-02-21T18:13:11.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-06T14:21:32.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.reddit.com/r/calvinandhobbes/comments/18pxhy/i_cant_believe_i_am_doing_this_but_what_exactly/c8gy9yp" target="_blank">This comment on reddit</a> sums up Calvin and Hobbes really well.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>I&#8217;ll tell you why. It&#8217;s because Watterson understood so much about the world. And not only was he able to understand so much, but he was able to present it in a way that made sense to everyone. He was teaching you, without you even noticing he was teaching you. And his medium for teaching was so incredibly brilliant and subtle, that I would bet most people didn&#8217;t appreciate how brilliant it was.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s important to note that Hobbes is completely and entirely a figment of Calvin&#8217;s imagination. He wasn&#8217;t like, magically alive in this alternate fantasy universe; Calvin exists here, in the same world that you and I live in. Watterson didn&#8217;t treat this like any other &#8216;imaginary friend&#8217; relationship either, he used it as a way to illustrate the thought process that we go through without even noticing.</p>
<p>When Calvin is speaking to Hobbes, he&#8217;s speaking to himself. When Hobbes responds to Calvin, it is Calvin thinking of ideas and being creative. Hobbes has his own personality and it is actually the personality of the inner-Calvin. And Watterson is incredibly consistent with this, he never deviates from this relationship. He never gives Hobbes ideas or responses that wouldn&#8217;t be natural for Calvin to make. A regular Calvin &amp; Hobbes discussion follows the same pattern as thought development in your own head.</p>
<p>Calvin is an implementation of Bill Watterson himself, thinking of ideas and making reflections on the world, but Watterson used the medium of cartoons to write his ideas. He came up with an ingenious method for illustrating his own inner-self battling with the ideas that the world gives to him. For that, I would argue that Watterson is one of the greatest psychologists of all time. He not only understood how the brain and thought work, but he came up with a metaphor for the process that would allow him to literally illustrate his thoughts. And his thoughts make me jealous of how brilliant he is. You read his stuff, and he has ideas about everything, he is an artistic thinker. I think of Contact and the line &#8216;so beautiful&hellip; there are no words&hellip; they should&#8217;ve sent a poet&#8217;. Watterson is that poet. He is the man who is able to take thoughts that are difficult for people to describe, and put words/pictures to them. It&#8217;s much easier to illustrate inner-conflict and idea development if you have two characters acting out the two sides of an idea, as well as how ideas progress and come to be. Imagine Watterson was just like other philosophers/thinkers and wrote a big heavy book about what he thinks of life, politics, relationships, science, etc. No one would read that, but millions of people read his comics.</p>
<p>I clued into all of this during my reading of the series, which I read all of in just a month back in the fall. I had never read them before, and I couldn&#8217;t stop. This concept that Watterson created was made apparent to me after reading a bunch of the &#8216;death by wagon ride&#8217; strips. In these strips (of which there are many), Calvin and Hobbes are riding through near death and neither of them are scared, excited, or otherwise phased at all. But, the entire ride, Calvin is making a monologue about some idea that just occurred to him. Hobbes, being Calvin&#8217;s inner-self, is completely unphased by the ride because he&#8217;s focusing on the ideas Calvin is creating. He should be flipping out and yelling at Calvin to slow down, but instead, he&#8217;s just patiently listening to what Calvin has to say. Just as our subconscious would.</p>
<p>There are so many other great details about this relationship that Watterson makes. Such as Calvin leaving Hobbes at home whenever he goes to school. Along with the many comments Calvin makes about the poor quality of education he&#8217;s getting, he also leaves Hobbes, his intelligent and helpful side, at home. The American education is so factually based that he has no need to bring the part of his brain that helps form new ideas with him to school. There&#8217;s no need for Calvin to think critically, the school doesn&#8217;t demand it of him. But I guarantee that most readers noticed the difference between at-home Calvin and in-school Calvin. Outside school, he&#8217;s making dramatic and insightful ideas about life, science, politics, etc., but in school, it&#8217;s just snarky and sarcastic Calvin that just talks about how his education is failing him. And they probably wondered how Calvin can be so smart at home, but can&#8217;t do well in school. It&#8217;s because Calvin leaves his critically thinking brain at home.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s also incredibly obvious with their handling of Susie, Calvin&#8217;s &#8216;love interest&#8217;. Calvin treats her like all prepubescent boys treat girls and their cooties. Hobbes, Calvin&#8217;s subconscious, is the only one that notices how nice, pretty, and awesome Susie is. When I was a kid, I was a shit to other girls, but I recognized in the back of my mind when I liked a girl. That&#8217;s my Hobbes, taunting me about how much I actually like her. Hobbes doesn&#8217;t just happen to like Susie and think she&#8217;s cute when Calvin is a bitch to her, the two go hand in hand.</p>
<p>Hobbes will often act as the moral, safe, and responsible side of Calvin too. All of us have a subconscious telling us when something looks dangerous as fuck, or would result in other people getting hurt, some people just don&#8217;t listen to it.</p>
<p>There are also two other important components of C&amp;H&#8217;s world-wide love, both are much, much easier to notice. First is Watterson&#8217;s treatment of IP and respect for his fans as well as the integrity of his creation. He wrote these strips everyday for ten years, and when he thought he was getting close to repeating ideas or using ideas of lesser quality, he stopped writing. He didn&#8217;t dilute his creation, he kept it A-list, which is how it will always be remembered. And the other point, is that they were relatable, which is even more mind-bogglingly genius. Watterson managed to create a metaphor for human thought that can be related to everyone&#8217;s childhood? Goddammit, how!?! Everyone remembers not wanting to wake up for school. Everyone remembers wishing for snow days. Everyone remembers having bad days and wanting to kill everyone. Everyone remembers going places and doing things that they didn&#8217;t want to do. Everyone remembers questioning the stupid rules and seemingly ambiguous regulations that our parents gave us. All of us relate to Calvin, and by extension, Watterson.</p>
<p>Everything went right with Calvin and Hobbes; the art, the flow, the topics, the humor, everything. It was one of those one in a million gems that you see just a couple of times in your life. Nothing is perfect, but Calvin and Hobbes was as close to perfect as I can imagine.</p>
</blockquote>
]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Writing" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Writing/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[On Web Design]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-web-design/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-web-design/</id>
    <published>2013-02-19T18:13:41.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-08T15:44:47.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p><a href="http://nesoupfactorysalem.com/soups-of-the-day/" target="_blank">This is my favorite website</a>. I visit it almost every day. It&#8217;s not responsive. It&#8217;s not optimized for iPhone. It looks blurry on a Retina display. It doesn&#8217;t use the latest HTML5/CSS3 framework. It doesn&#8217;t have a thoughtful vertical rhythm. The fonts are nothing special. It is neither skeumorphic nor flat. It doesn&#8217;t have its own favicon. It doesn&#8217;t have a native app or Twitter or Instagram. It doesn&#8217;t use AJAX or SCRUM or node.js or Sinatra. It doesn&#8217;t have an API or an RSS feed or VC funding. It hasn&#8217;t been featured on a prominent tech blog or won an award.</p>
<p>It tells me the soups of the day.</p>
<p>Freely distributed information that&#8217;s relevant to the person reading it. That&#8217;s web design.</p>
</blockquote>
<div class="source"><a href="http://simplebits.com/notebook/2013/02/16/food-for-thought/" target="_blank">Food for Thought</a> <em>by</em> Dan Cederholm</div>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Being Responsive]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/being-responsive/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/being-responsive/</id>
    <published>2013-01-03T08:59:37.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-05T15:57:19.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I have modified this site a little. A small step towards truly formless content. Resize the browser window or get here through a decent mobile device browser (not you blackberry!) to see it in action.</p>
]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Writing" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Writing/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Peppertones]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/peppertones/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/peppertones/</id>
    <published>2012-12-31T04:06:53.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-18T23:25:43.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class="excerpt"><p>Peppertones (Hangul: 페퍼톤스), is a Korean electronic/house duo. I don&#8217;t usually listen to Korean music but this one is hard to resist. At first I only listen to their English songs because I do not understand Korean, but then I tried listening to some of the Korean songs and I am hooked. I can listen to their fun and catchy tunes all day long at work, err while working that is.</p>
<p>Here are some of my favourites</p>
<iframe width="864" height="468" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/rqKzwsfeTJI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

</div><!-- excerpt -->

<iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/Q2wJw-7Silk" width="864" height="468" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></content>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Peppertones (Hangul: 페퍼톤스), is a Korean electronic/house duo. I don&#8217;t usually listen to Korean music but this one is hard to resist. At first I only listen to their English songs because I do not understand Korean, but then I tried listening to some of the Korean songs and I am hooked. I can listen to their fun and catchy tunes all day long at work, err while working that is.</p>
<p>Here are some of my favourites</p>
<iframe width="864" height="468" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/rqKzwsfeTJI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></summary>
    
      <category term="Music" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Music/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[On The Time You’ll Remember]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-the-time-you-ll-remember/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-the-time-you-ll-remember/</id>
    <published>2012-11-27T07:04:19.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-18T07:44:20.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>Because in the end, you won&#8217;t remember the time you spent working in the office or mowing your lawn. <br/>Climb that goddamn mountain.</p>
</blockquote>
<div class="source">Jack Kerouac, author</div>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Banda Neira]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/banda-neira/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/banda-neira/</id>
    <published>2012-11-11T16:18:13.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-19T00:06:11.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I found Banda Neira on a random browsing session not so long ago and they instantly become one of my favourite. Though they said that their songs are mostly sad, they are surprisingly good and highly enjoyable. Here is one of their latest live show.</p>
<p><iframe src="http://player.vimeo.com/video/52933791?badge=0&amp;color=aaaaaa" frameborder="0" width="864" height="468" webkitAllowFullScreen mozallowfullscreen allowFullScreen></iframe><p class="caption"><a href="http://vimeo.com/52933791" target="_blank">‘Di Paruh Waktu show’ Banda Neira - Tanpa Cerita</a> from <a href="http://vimeo.com/user14521423" target="_blank">Joeroe Rekam</a>.</p></p>
<p>Find more of them <a href="http://www.soundcloud.com/bandaneira" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Music" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Music/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[On Sincerity]]></title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-sincerity/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-sincerity/</id>
    <published>2012-10-29T18:43:12.000Z</published>
    <updated>2014-01-18T07:43:59.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>My brother, if you desire the path of sincerity, flee from the clatter and clinks of fame, and flee from the clamour that comes with being a celebrity. Be like the roots of a tree; it keeps the tree upright and gives it life, but it itself is hidden underneath the earth and eyes cannot see it. Or be like the foundations of a building; were it not for the foundation, no wall could be erected and no house could be established, but yet no&ndash;one sees the foundation.</p>
</blockquote>
<div class="source">Al&ndash;Niyyah wal&ndash;Ikhlas <em>by</em> Dr. al&ndash;Qaradlawi</div>]]></content>
    
    
      <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
