<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Meanwhile</title>
  
  <subtitle>Journal • Thoughts • Favourites</subtitle>
  <link href="http://widatama.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://widatama.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2022-07-05T04:07:06.682Z</updated>
  <id>http://widatama.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Danu Widatama</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>On Social Network</title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-social-network/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-social-network/</id>
    <published>2016-01-26T07:01:12.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-05T04:07:06.682Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>The question of identity has changed from being something you are born with to a task: you have to create your own community. But communities aren’t created, and you either have one or you don’t. What the social networks can create is a substitute. The difference between a community and a network is that you belong to a community, but a network belongs to you. You feel in control. You can add friends if you wish, you can delete them if you wish. You are in control of the important people to whom you relate. People feel a little better as a result, because loneliness, abandonment, is the great fear in our individualist age. But it’s so easy to add or remove friends on the internet that people fail to learn the real social skills, which you need when you go to the street, when you go to your workplace, where you find lots of people who you need to enter into sensible interaction with. Pope Francis, who is a great man, gave his first interview after being elected to Eugenio Scalfari, an Italian journalist who is also a self-proclaimed atheist. It was a sign: real dialogue isn’t about talking to people who believe the same things as you. Social media don’t teach us to dialogue because it is so easy to avoid controversy… But most people use social media not to unite, not to open their horizons wider, but on the contrary, to cut themselves a comfort zone where the only sounds they hear are the echoes of their own voice, where the only things they see are the reflections of their own face. Social media are very useful, they provide pleasure, but they are a trap.</p></blockquote><div class="source"><a href="https://elpais.com/elpais/2016/01/19/inenglish/1453208692_424660.html">Zygmunt Bauman</a>, Sociologist</div>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The question of identity has changed from being something you are born with to a task: you have to create your own community</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>On Materialism</title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-materialism/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-materialism/</id>
    <published>2015-12-13T15:44:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-05T06:55:40.383Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>I have taken fuel merely as an example to illustrate a very simple thesis: that economic growth, which viewed from the point of view of economics, physics, chemistry and technology, has no discernible limit, must necessarily run into decisive bottlenecks when viewed from the point of view of the environmental sciences. An attitude to life which seeks fulfilment in the single-minded pursuit of wealth—in short, materialism—does not fit into this world, because it contains within itself no limiting principle, while the environment in which it is placed is strictly limited. Already, the environment is trying to tell us that certain stresses are becoming excessive. As one problem is being ‘solved’. ten new problems arise as a result of the first ‘solution’. As Professor Barry Commoner emphasises, the new problems are not the consequences of incidental failure but of technological success.</p></blockquote><div class="source">Small Is Beautiful: Economics as if People Mattered <em>by</em> Ernst F. Schumacher</div>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have taken fuel merely as an example to illustrate a very simple thesis: that economic growth, which viewed from the point</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Emi Meyer and The Shanghai Restoration Project</title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/emi-meyer/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/emi-meyer/</id>
    <published>2014-07-05T08:37:40.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-05T04:07:06.680Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Good music and exquisite voice. Perfect summer song.</p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/2as7ldIdWFs" width="864" height="468" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Good music and exquisite voice. Perfect summer song.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2as7ldIdWFs&quot; width=&quot;864&quot; height=&quot;468&quot;</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Music" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Music/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>On The Price of Success</title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-the-price-of-success/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-the-price-of-success/</id>
    <published>2014-06-19T02:42:39.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-05T04:18:16.241Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>When you have nothing, you don’t fear being torn to shreds by the mob. You stand up and you call bullshit when you see it. But then when you start to do well… when you start to make a name for yourself… when you start to make money or have a certain number of Twitter followers, the spotlight turns to you.</p><p>You start to be more diplomatic and politically correct. You start to mould yourself into the shape of what everyone else expects you to be, because if you aren’t that, then the mob is waiting like it’s Lord of The fucking Flies.</p><p>Electric fences start to pop up all around you. Issues which you don’t even go near because touching them, in any way, is fatal. You can’t talk about sexism any more, because one wrong move there is career-ending. You don’t call out the bullshit industry awards, because you’re nominated to win some of them. You fail to draw attention to the morally bankrupt venture capitalists and journalists, because then they might not write about you or give you money any more.</p><p>So you mellow. And slowly but surely you turn into the very thing that you once rebelled against so strongly in your first album. When you had a voice. When you actually fucking stood for something.</p><p>And then you can’t talk about anything any more. The fear has taken over. All hope of the change that you once so strongly believed in has now been lost.</p><p><strong>The price of success is censorship. We bring it on ourselves, and we enforce it on others with this giant pyramid scheme which we call “life”.</strong></p><p>…</p><p><strong>The price of success is this: You have two choices. Join the bullshit facade and plod along as another sheep in the capitalist machine, doing whatever it takes to maintain your position—or stand up for something you believe in, and accept every kick, punch and vicious attack on who you are.</strong></p></blockquote><div class="source"><a href="https://john.onolan.org/the-price-of-success/">The Price of Success</a> <em>by</em> John O’Nolan</div>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you have nothing, you don’t fear being torn to shreds by the mob. You stand up and you call bullshit when you see it. B</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Tribute to Vignelli</title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/tribute-to-vignelli/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/tribute-to-vignelli/</id>
    <published>2014-05-28T00:59:51.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-05T04:07:06.684Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p><span class="scream">In a world where everybody screams</span>, <span class="silence">silence</span> <span class="scream">is noticeable.</span></p></blockquote><div class="source"><a href="https://observatory.designobserver.com/feature/massimo-vignelli-1931-2014/38336/">Massimo Vignelli, 1931&ndash;2014</a></div>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;scream&quot;&gt;In a world where everybody screams&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span class=&quot;silence&quot;&gt;silence&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;scream&quot;&gt;is</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>On The Caring Ones</title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-the-caring-ones/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-the-caring-ones/</id>
    <published>2014-05-09T02:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-05T04:18:16.240Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>Realize that nobody cares, and if they do, you shouldn’t care that they care. Got a new car? Nobody cares. You’ll get some gawkers for a couple of weeks—they don’t care. They’re curious. Three weeks in it’ll be just another shiny blob among all the thousands of others crawling down the freeway and sitting in garages and driveways up and down your street. People will care about your car just as much as you care about all of those. Got a new gewgaw? New wardrobe? Went to a swanky restaurant? Exotic vacation? Nobody cares. Don’t base your happiness on people caring, because they won’t. And if they do, they either want your stuff or hate you for it.</p><p>Occasionally, people in your life will defy the odds and actually care about you. Still not your stuff, sorry. But if they value you, they’ll value that you value it, and they’ll listen. When you talk about all of those things that nobody else cares about,<br/>they will look into your eyes and consume your words, and in that moment you will know that every part of them is there with you.</p><p>Marry them. Befriend them. Work with them. Spend weekends with them. No matter how much power you become possessed of, you’ll never be able to make someone care—so gather close the caring.</p></blockquote><div class="source"><a href="https://www.quora.com/Justin-Freeman">Justin Freeman</a> <em>on</em> <a href="https://www.quora.com/Life/What-are-the-top-10-things-that-we-should-be-informed-about-in-life">Quora</a></div>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Realize that nobody cares, and if they do, you shouldn’t care that they care. Got a new car? Nobody cares. You’ll get some g</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Stop Your Crying</title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/stop-your-crying/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/stop-your-crying/</id>
    <published>2014-04-17T01:43:03.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-05T04:18:16.242Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These guys never fail to amaze me…</p><iframe width="864" height="468" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/UcVbkiVZg7U" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;These guys never fail to amaze me…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;864&quot; height=&quot;468&quot; src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/UcVbkiVZg7U&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfu</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Music" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Music/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Luckiest</title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/the-luckiest/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/the-luckiest/</id>
    <published>2014-02-11T14:30:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-05T04:18:16.242Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I was watching <a href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt2194499">About Time</a> a couple of days ago and this song came out. Ben Folds makes some really good music, this one is certainly a favourite.</p><iframe width="864" height="468" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/2L10oVwGwIA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I was watching &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt2194499&quot;&gt;About Time&lt;/a&gt; a couple of days ago and this song came out. Ben Folds makes</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Music" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Music/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>On Our Attention to Life</title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/on-our-attention-to-life/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/on-our-attention-to-life/</id>
    <published>2014-02-01T23:22:56.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-05T04:07:06.681Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>We have these brief lives, and our only real choice is how we will fill them. Your attention is precious. Don’t squander it. Don’t throw it away. Don’t let companies and products steal it from you. Don’t let advertisers trick you into lusting after things you don’t need. Don’t let the media convince you to covet the lives of celebrities. Own your attention—it’s all you really have.</p></blockquote><div class="source"><a href="https://transom.org/?p=41667">Navigating Stuckness</a> <em>by</em> Jonathan Harris</div>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have these brief lives, and our only real choice is how we will fill them. Your attention is precious. Don’t squander it.</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Words" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Words/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Static Temptation</title>
    <link href="http://widatama.github.io/the-static-temptation/"/>
    <id>http://widatama.github.io/the-static-temptation/</id>
    <published>2014-01-19T00:59:18.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-05T04:07:06.684Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I have been exploring the options for making this whole site content static. The initial set up is quite a hassle but afterwards there are less things to take care of and less to worry about.</p><p>So here it is, static contents made with <a href="https://zespia.tw/hexo">Hexo</a> and hosted on <a href="http://pages.github.com/">Github Pages</a>.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have been exploring the options for making this whole site content static. The initial set up is quite a hassle but afterwards there ar</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Writing" scheme="http://widatama.github.io/categories/Writing/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
